this is a 3 it's sloppily
这是3号，太草率了。
written and rendered at an extremely low resolution of
以极低的分辨率编写和呈现
28 by 28 pixels
28乘28像素
but your brain has no trouble recognizing it as a 3
但你的大脑很容易把它识别为3
and I want you to take a moment to appreciate
我希望你花点时间欣赏
how crazy it is
这有多疯狂
that brains can do this so effortlessly
大脑可以毫不费力地做到这一点
I mean this
我是说这个
this and this are also recognizable as threes
这个和这个也可以识别为三
even though the specific values of each pixel
即使每个像素的具体值
is very different from one image to the next
从一个图像到下一个图像非常不同
the particular light
特定的光
sensitive cells in your eye that are firing
你眼睛里的敏感细胞在放电
when you see this
当你看到这个
threes are very different from the ones firing
3跟开火的很不一样
when you see this threes
当你看到这个三
but something
但是有些东西
in that crazy smart visual cortex of yours
在你那疯狂聪明的视觉皮层里
resolves these as representing the same idea
将这些解析为代表相同的想法
while at the same time recognizing other images
同时识别其他图像
as their own distinct ideas
作为他们自己独特的想法
but if I told you hey
但如果我告诉你嘿
sit down and write for me a program
坐下来给我写个程序
that takes in a grid of 28 by 28 pixels like this
它采用像这样的28 x 28像素的网格
and outputs a single number between 0 and 10
并输出0到10之间的单个数字
telling you what it thinks the digit is
告诉你它认为数字是什么
well the task goes from comically trivial
这个任务从滑稽的琐碎
to dauntingly difficult
极其困难
unless you've been living under a rock
除非你一直生活在岩石下
I think I hardly need to motivate
我想我几乎不需要激励
the relevance and importance of machine learning
机器学习的相关性和重要性
and neural networks
和神经网络
to the present and to the future
到现在和未来
but what I want to do here
但是我想在这里做的是
is show you what a neural network actually is
向你展示什么是神经网络
assuming no background
假设没有背景
and to help visualize what it's doing
并帮助想象它在做什么
not as a buzzword but as a piece of math
不是作为一个流行词，而是作为一个数学
my hope is just that you come away
我只希望你能离开
feeling like the structure itself is motivated
感觉结构本身是有动机的
and to feel like you know what it means when you read
当你阅读时，感觉你知道这意味着什么
or you hear about a neural network learning
或者你听说过神经网络学习
this video is just going to be devoted to the structure
这段视频将专门介绍结构
component of that
组成部分
and the following one is going to tackle learning
下面这个将解决学习问题
what we're going to do is put together a neural network
我们要做的是组合一个神经网络
that can learn to recognize handwritten digits
可以学习识别手写数字
this is a somewhat classic example
这是一个有点经典的例子
for introducing the topic
介绍主题
and I'm happy to stick with the status quo here
我很乐意维持现状
because at the end of the two videos
因为在两个视频的结尾
I want to point you to a couple good resources
我想给你们介绍一些有用的资源
where you can learn more
在那里您可以了解更多信息
and where you can download the code that does this
以及您可以在哪里下载执行此操作的代码
and play with it on your own computer
并在自己的电脑上玩它
there are many
有很多
many variants of neural networks
神经网络的许多变种
and in recent years
近年来
there's been
已经有了
sort of a boom in research towards these variants
对这些变体的研究热潮
but in these two introductory videos
但在这两个介绍性视频中
you and I are just going to look at the simplest
你和我只看最简单的
plain vanilla form with no added frills
没有额外褶边的普通香草形式
this is kind of a necessary prerequisite
这是一个必要的先决条件
for understanding any of the more powerful
了解任何更强大的
modern variants
现代变体
and trust me it still has plenty of complexity
相信我，它仍然有很多复杂性
for us to wrap our minds around
让我们把思想包裹起来
but even in this simplest form
但即使是最简单的形式
it can learn to recognize handwritten digits
它可以学习识别手写数字
which is a pretty cool thing
这是一件很酷的事情
for a computer to be able to do
让计算机能够做到
and at the same time
同时
you'll see how it does fall short
你会看到它是如何不足的
of a couple hopes that we might have for it
我们可能会有一些希望
as the name suggests
顾名思义
neural networks are inspired by the brain
神经网络受大脑启发
but let's break that down
但是让我们把它分解一下。
what are the neurons
神经元是什么？
and in what sense are they linked together
它们在什么意义上联系在一起？
right now when I say neuron
现在当我说神经元的时候
all I want you to think about is
我想让你想的是
a thing that holds a number
有数字的东西
specifically a number between 0 and 1
特别是0到1之间的数字
it's really not more than that
真的不止这些
for example the network starts
例如网络启动
with a bunch of neurons
用一堆神经元
corresponding to each of the 28
对应于28个中的每一个
times 28 pixels of the input image
乘以输入图像的28像素
which is 784 neurons in total
总共有784个神经元
each one of these holds a number
每一个都有一个数字
that represents the grayscale value
表示灰度值
of the corresponding pixel
对应像素的
ranging from
从
0 for black pixels up to 1 for white pixels
黑色像素为0，白色像素为1
this number inside the neuron is called its activation
神经元内部的这个数字称为它的激活
and the image you might have in mind here is that
你脑海中的画面可能是
each neuron is lit up
每个神经元都被点亮
when its activation is a high number
当它的激活是一个高数字时
so all of these 784 neurons
所以所有这784个神经元
make up the first layer of our network
构成我们网络的第一层
now jumping over to the last layer
现在跳到最后一层
this has 10 neurons
它有10个神经元
each representing one of the digits
每个代表一个数字
the activation in these neurons
这些神经元的激活
again some number that's between 0 and 1
又是一个介于0和1之间的数字
represents
代表
how much the system thinks that a given image
系统认为给定图像有多少
corresponds with a given digit
对应给定的数字
there's also a couple layers in between
中间还有几层
called the hidden layers
称为隐藏层
which for the time being
暂时
should just be a giant question Mark for how on earth
马克，这应该是一个巨大的问题
this process of recognizing digits
这种识别数字的过程
is going to be handled
将被处理
in this network I chose two hidden layers
在这个网络中，我选择了两个隐藏层
each one with 16 neurons
每一个都有16个神经元
and admittedly that's kind of an arbitrary choice
诚然，这是一个武断的选择。
to be honest I chose two layers
说实话我选了两层
based on how I want to motivate the structure
基于我想如何激励结构
in just a moment
就在一瞬间
and 16
和16
well that was just a nice number to fit on the screen
嗯，这只是一个适合屏幕的漂亮数字。
in practice there is a lot of room for experiment
在实践中有很大的实验空间
with a specific structure here
这里有一个特定的结构
the way the network operates
网络运作方式
activations in one layer
一层激活
determine the activations of the next layer
确定下一层的激活
and of course
当然还有
the heart of the network
网络的核心
as an information processing mechanism
作为一种信息处理机制
comes down to exactly how
归结为到底是如何
those activations from one layer
那些来自一层的激活
bring about activations in the next layer
在下一层激活
it's meant to be
这是命中注定的
loosely analogous to how
大致类似于
in biological networks of neurons
在神经元的生物网络中
some groups of neurons firing
一些神经元群放电
cause certain others to fire
使某些其他人开火
now the network I'm showing here
现在我在这里展示的网络
has already been trained to recognize digits
已经接受过识别数字的训练
and let me show you what I mean by that
让我告诉你我的意思
it means if you feed in an image
这意味着如果您输入图像
lighting up all 784 neurons of the input layer
点亮输入层的所有784个神经元
according to the brightness of each pixel in the image
根据图像中每个像素的亮度
that pattern of activations
这种激活模式
causes some very specific pattern in the next layer
在下一层中导致一些非常特定的模式
which causes some pattern in the one after it
这导致了之后的一些模式
which finally gives some pattern in the output layer
这最终在输出层给出了一些模式
and the brightest neuron of that output layer
输出层中最亮的神经元
is the network's choice
是网络的选择
so to speak for what digit this image represents
所以说这张图片代表什么数字
and before jumping into the math
在进入数学之前
for how one layer influences the next
一层如何影响下一层
or how training works
或者培训是如何运作的
let's just talk about why
让我们谈谈为什么
it's even reasonable
这甚至是合理的
to expect a layered structure like this
期待这样的分层结构
to behave intelligently
聪明地行事
what are we expecting here
我们在这里期待什么？
what is the best hope
最好的希望是什么
for what those middle layers might be doing
中间层可能在做什么
well when you or I recognize digits
好吧，当你或我识别数字时
we piece together various components
我们将各种组件拼凑在一起
a 9 has a loop up top and a line on the right
A 9顶部有一个环，右侧有一条线
an 8 also has a loop up top
A 8顶部也有一个环
but it's paired with another loop down low
但它与另一个低循环配对
a 4 basically breaks down into three specific lines
A4基本上可以分为三行
and things like that
诸如此类的事情
now in a perfect world
现在在一个完美的世界里
we might hope that each neuron
我们可能希望每个神经元
in the second to last layer
在倒数第二层
corresponds with one of these sub components
对应于这些子组件之一
that anytime you feed in an image with say
每当您输入带有say的图像时
a loop up top
一个循环
like a 9 or an 8
比如9号或8号。
there's some specific neuron
有一些特定的神经元
whose activation is going to be close to one
谁的激活将接近一个
and I don't mean this specific loop of pixels
我不是指这个特定的像素循环
the hope would be that
希望是
any generally loopy pattern towards the top
任何朝向顶部的普遍环状图案
sets off this neuron
刺激这个神经元
that way going from the third layer to the last one
从第三层到最后一层
just requires learning
只是需要学习
which combination of subcomponents
哪个子组件的组合
corresponds to which digits
对应于哪些数字
of course that just kicks the problem down the road
当然，这只是把问题抛在脑后。
because how would you recognize these subcomponents
因为你如何识别这些子组件？
or even learn what the right subcomponents should be
甚至了解正确的子组件应该是什么
and I still haven't even
我甚至还没有
talked about how one layer influences the next
谈到了一层如何影响下一层
but run with me on this one for a moment
但这次和我一起跑一会儿
recognizing a loop can also break down into subproblems
识别循环也可以分解为子问题
one reasonable way to do this
做到这一点的一种合理方法
would be to first recognize the various little edges
就是首先识别出不同的小边缘
that make it up
那是编造的
similarly
类似地
a long line like the kind you might see in the digits 1
一条长线，就像你可能在数字1中看到的那种。
or 4 or 7 well that's really just a long edge
或者4或7，这真的只是一个很长的边缘。
or maybe you think of it as a certain pattern
或者你认为这是一种特定的模式
of several smaller edges
几个较小的边缘
so maybe our hope is that each neuron
所以也许我们希望每个神经元
in the second layer of the network
在网络的第二层
corresponds with the various relevant little edges
对应于各种相关的小边缘
maybe when an image like this one comes in
也许当这样的图像出现时
it lights up all of the neurons associated with
它点亮所有相关的神经元
around eight to 10 specific little edges
大约8到10个特定的小边缘
which in turn
反过来
lights up the neurons associated with the upper loop
点亮与上环相关的神经元
and a long vertical line
和一条长长的垂直线
and those light up the neuron associated with a 9
这些点亮与9相关的神经元
whether or not
是否
this is what our final network actually does
这就是我们最终的网络实际上所做的
is another question
是另一个问题
one that I'll come back to
一个我会回来的
once we see how to train the network
一旦我们知道如何训练网络
but this is a hope that we might have
但这是我们可能有的希望
a sort of goal with the layered structure like this
一种像这样分层结构的目标
moreover
此外
you can imagine how being able to detect edges
你可以想象如何能够检测边缘
and patterns like this
和这样的图案
would be really useful
会很有用。
for other image recognition tasks
用于其他图像识别任务
and even beyond image recognition
甚至超越图像识别
there are all sorts of intelligent things
有各种各样的智能事物
you might want to do
你可能想做
that break down into layers of abstraction
分解成抽象层
parsing speech for example
例如解析语音
involves taking raw audio
涉及获取原始音频
and picking out distinct sounds
并挑选出独特的声音
which combine to make certain syllables
组合成特定的音节
which combine to form words
组合成单词
which combine to make up phrases
它们结合起来组成短语
and more abstract thoughts etc
以及更抽象的想法等
but getting back to how any of this actually works
但回到这一切实际上是如何运作的
picture yourself right now designing
想象自己现在正在设计
how exactly the activations in one layer
一层中的激活到底是如何
might determine the activations in the next
可能会决定下一次的激活
the goal is to have some mechanism
目标是有一些机制
that could conceivably combine pixels into edges
可以想象将像素组合成边缘
or edges into patterns or patterns into digits
或边缘变成图案或图案变成数字
and to zoom in on one very specific example
并放大一个非常具体的例子
let's say the hope is for one particular neuron
假设希望是某个特定的神经元
in the second layer
在第二层
to pick up on whether or not the image has an edge
判断图像是否有边缘
in this region here
在这个地区这里
the question at hand is
眼前的问题是
what parameters should the network have
网络应该有哪些参数
what dials and knobs should you be able to tweak
您应该能够调整哪些表盘和旋钮
so that it's expressive enough
这样就足够有表现力了
to potentially capture this pattern
潜在地捕捉到这种模式
or any other pixel pattern
或任何其他像素图案
or the pattern that several edges can make
或者几个边缘可以制作的图案
a loop and other such things
循环和其他类似的东西
but what we'll do
但是我们要做的
is assign a weight
是分配一个权重
to each one of the connections between our neuron
我们神经元之间的每一个连接
and the neurons from the first layer
和第一层的神经元
these weights are just numbers
这些权重只是数字
then
然后
take all of those activations from the first layer
从第一层开始所有这些激活
and compute their weighted sum
并计算它们的加权和
according to these weights
根据这些权重
I find it helpful
我觉得很有帮助
to think of these
想到这些
weights as being organized into a little grid
权重被组织成一个小网格
of their own and I'm going to use green
他们自己的，我要用绿色的。
pixels to indicate positive weights
像素表示正权重
and red pixels to indicate negative weights
和红色像素表示负权重
where the brightness of that pixel is
该像素的亮度在哪里
some loose depiction of the weights value
权重值的一些松散描述
now if we made the weights associated with
现在，如果我们将权重与
almost all of the pixels 0
几乎所有的像素都是0
except for some positive weights
除了一些正权重
in this region that we care about
在这个我们关心的地区
then taking the weighted sum of all the pixel values
然后取所有像素值的加权和
really just amounts to adding up
真的只是加起来
the values of the pixel
像素的值
just in the region that we care about
就在我们关心的地区
and if you really wanted to pick up on
如果你真的想了解
whether there's an edge here
这里是否有优势
what you might do is
你可能会做的是
have some negative weights
负重
associated with the surrounding pixels
与周围像素相关联
then
然后
the sum is largest when those middle pixels are bright
当中间像素明亮时，总和最大
but the surrounding pixels are darker
但周围像素较暗
when you compute a weighted sum like this
当你计算这样的加权和时
you might come out with any number
你可能会得到任何数字
but for this network
但对于这个网络
what we want is for activations to be
我们想要的是激活
some value between 0 and 1
0到1之间的某个值
so a common thing to do is to pump this weighted sum
所以一个常见的做法是泵这个加权和
into some function
进入某种功能
that squishes the real number line
压扁真实数字线
into the range between 0 and one
进入0到1之间的范围
and a common function that does this is called
执行此操作的常用函数称为
the sigmoid function
sigmoid函数
also known as a logistic curve
也称为逻辑曲线
basically very negative inputs end up close to 0
基本上非常负的输入最终接近0
very positive inputs end up close to 1
非常正的输入最终接近1
and it just steadily increases around the input zero
它只是在输入零附近稳步增加
so the activation of the neuron here
所以这里神经元的激活
is basically a measure of how positive
基本上是衡量有多积极
the relevant weighted sum is
相关加权和为
but maybe it's not that
但也许不是那样
you want the neuron to light up
你想让神经元亮起来
when the weighted sum is bigger than 0
当加权和大于0时
maybe you only want it to be active
也许你只是想让它活跃起来
when the sum is bigger than say 10
当总和大于10时
that is you want some bias for it to be inactive
那就是你想要一些偏见让它不活跃。
what we'll do then is just add in some other number
然后我们要做的就是添加一些其他数字
like negative 10 to
喜欢负10到
this weighted sum
这个加权和
before plugging it through the sigmoid
在插入乙状结肠之前
squishification function
压扁函数
that additional number is called the bias
这个额外的数字称为偏差
so the weights
所以重量
tell you what pixel pattern
告诉你什么像素图案
this neuron in the second layer is picking up on
第二层的神经元正在接收
and the bias
和偏见
tells you how high the weighted sum needs to be
告诉你加权和需要多高
before the neuron starts getting meaningfully active
在神经元开始有意义地活跃之前
and that is just one neuron
这只是一个神经元
every other neuron in this layer
这一层的每个其他神经元
is going to be connected to all
将连接到所有
784 pixel neurons from the first layer
来自第一层的784个像素神经元
and each one of those 784 connections
这784个连接中的每一个
has its own weight associated with it
有它自己的重量
also each one has some bias
每个人都有一些偏见
some other number
其他号码
that you add on to the weighted sum
你加上加权和
before squishing it with the sigmoid
在用乙状结肠压扁它之前
and that's a lot to think about
要考虑的事情太多了
with this hidden layer of 16 neurons
有了这16个神经元的隐藏层
that's a total of 784
一共是784个
times 16 weights along with 16 biases
乘以16个权重和16个偏差
and all of that
所有这些
is just the connections
只是连接
from the first layer to the second
从第一层到第二层
the connections between the other layers
其他层之间的连接
also have a bunch of weights
也有一堆重量
and biases associated with them
以及与之相关的偏见
all said and done
说到做到
this network has almost exactly
这个网络几乎完全
13,000 total weights and biases
13,000个总权重和偏差
13,000 knobs and dials
13,000个旋钮和表盘
that can be tweaked
可以调整
and turned
并转向
to make this network behave in different ways
使这个网络以不同的方式运行
so when we talk about learning
所以当我们谈论学习时
what that's referring to
那是指什么
is getting the computer to find a valid setting
正在让计算机找到一个有效的设置
for all of these many
对于所有这些许多
many numbers
许多数字
so that it'll actually solve the problem at hand
这样才能真正解决手头的问题
one thought experiment that is
一个思想实验就是
at once fun and kind of horrifying
既有趣又有点吓人
is to imagine sitting down
就是想象坐下来
and setting all of these weights and biases by hand
并手动设置所有这些权重和偏差
purposefully tweaking the numbers
故意调整数字
so that the second layer picks up on edges
以便第二层拾起边缘
the third layer picks up on patterns etc
第三层拾取图案等
I personally find this satisfying
我个人觉得这很令人满意
rather than just treating the network as a total
而不仅仅是将网络视为一个总数
black box because when the network doesn't perform
黑匣子，因为当网络不执行时
the way you anticipate
你预期的方式
if you've built up a little bit of a relationship
如果你已经建立了一点关系
with what those weights and biases actually mean
这些权重和偏差实际上意味着什么
you have a starting place for experimenting with
你有一个实验的起点
how to change the structure
如何改变结构
to improve or when the network does work
改进或当网络确实有效时
but not for the reasons you might expect
但不是因为你所期望的原因
digging into what the weights and biases are doing
深入研究权重和偏差在做什么
is a good way to challenge your assumptions
是挑战你的假设的好方法
and really expose the full space of possible solutions
并真正暴露出可能的解决方案的全部空间
by the way the actual function
顺便说一下实际功能
here is a little cumbersome to write down
这里写下来有点繁琐
don't you think
你不觉得
so let me show you
所以让我给你看看
a more notationally
更有注释性的
compact way that these connections are represented
表示这些连接的紧凑方式
this is how you'd see it
这就是你的看法
if you choose to read up more about neural
如果你选择阅读更多关于神经的知识
networks organize all of the activations from one layer
网络从一层组织所有激活
into a column as a vector
作为向量进入列
then organize all of the weights as a matrix
然后将所有权重组织为矩阵
where each row of that matrix
其中该矩阵的每一行
corresponds to the connections between one layer
对应一层之间的连接
and a particular neuron in the next layer
和下一层的特定神经元
what that means is that
这意味着
taking the weighted sum of the activations
取激活的加权和
in the first layer
在第一层
according to these weights
根据这些权重
corresponds to one of the terms
对应于其中一个术语
in the matrix vector product of everything
在万物的矩阵向量积中
we have on the left here
我们左边有
by the way so much of machine learning
顺便说一句，很多机器学习
just comes down to having a good grasp
归根结底就是要好好把握
of linear algebra
线性代数
so for any of you who want a nice
所以对于你们中任何想要一个好的
visual understanding for matrices
矩阵的视觉理解
and what matrix vector multiplication means
矩阵向量乘法是什么意思？
take a look at the series I did on linear algebra
看看我做的线性代数系列
especially chapter 3
尤其是第3章
back to our expression
回到我们的表情
instead of talking about adding the bias
而不是谈论增加偏见
to each one of these values
这些价值观中的每一个
independently
独立地
we represent it
我们代表它
by organizing all those biases into a vector
通过将所有这些偏差组织成一个向量
and adding the entire vector to the previous matrix
并将整个向量添加到前一个矩阵中
vector product
向量积
then as a final step
然后作为最后一步
I'll wrap a sigmoid around the outside here
我把乙状结肠包在外面
and what that's supposed to represent
那应该代表什么？
is that you're going
就是你要去
to apply the sigmoid function
应用sigmoid函数
to each specific component
到每个特定组件
of the resulting vector inside
里面的结果向量
so once you write down this weight matrix
所以一旦你写下这个权重矩阵
and these vectors as their own symbols
这些向量作为它们自己的符号
you can communicate
你可以交流
the full transition of activations
激活的完全过渡
from one layer to the next
从一层到下一层
in an extremely tight and neat little expression
以一种极其紧凑整洁的小表情
and this makes the relevant code both a lot simpler
这使得相关代码都变得简单多了
and a lot faster
而且要快得多
since many libraries
由于许多图书馆
optimize the heck out of matrix multiplication
优化矩阵乘法
remember how earlier I said
还记得我之前说过
these neurons are simply things that hold numbers
这些神经元只是简单的保存数字的东西
well of course
嗯，当然
the specific numbers that they hold
他们持有的具体数字
depends on the image you feed in
取决于您输入的图像
so it's actually more accurate
所以它实际上更准确
to think of each neuron as a function
将每个神经元视为一个函数
one that takes in the outputs
接受输出的人
of all the neurons in the previous layer
在前一层的所有神经元中
and spits out a number between 0 and 1
并吐出一个0到1之间的数字
really the entire network is just a function
真的，整个网络只是一个函数
one that takes in 784 numbers as an input
输入784个数字作为输入的数字
and spits out 10 numbers as an output
并吐出10个数字作为输出
it's an absurdly complicated function
这是一个非常复杂的函数
one that involves 13,000 parameters
一个涉及13,000个参数
in the forms of these weights
以这些重量的形式
and biases that pick up on certain patterns
以及对特定模式的偏见
and which involves iterating many matrix
这涉及迭代许多矩阵
vector products
向量积
and the sigmoid squishification function
和乙状结肠压扁功能
but it's just a function nonetheless
但它仍然只是一个函数
and in a way
在某种程度上
it's kind of reassuring that it looks complicated
它看起来很复杂，这让人放心。
I mean if it were any simpler
我是说如果再简单点
what hope would we have
我们还有什么希望
that it could take on
它可以承担
the challenge of recognizing digits
识别数字的挑战
and how does it take on that challenge
它是如何应对这一挑战的？
how does this network learn the appropriate weights
这个网络如何学习适当的权重
and biases just by looking at data
仅仅通过查看数据就会产生偏见
oh that's what I'll show in the next video
哦，这就是我将在下一个视频中展示的。
and I'll also dig a little more into
我还会深入挖掘
what this particular network
这个特定的网络是什么
we're seeing is really doing
我们看到的真的在做
now is the point
现在才是重点
I suppose I should say subscribe
我想我应该说订阅
to stay notified about when that video
随时通知该视频何时发布
or any new videos come out
或者任何新视频出来
but realistically
但实际上
most of you don't actually receive notifications
你们中的大多数人实际上并没有收到通知
from YouTube do you
来自YouTube，你呢？
maybe more honestly
也许更诚实
I should say subscribe
我应该说订阅
so that the neural networks that underlie
所以作为基础的神经网络
YouTube's recommendation algorithm
YouTube的推荐算法
are primed to believe that
已经准备好相信
you want to see content from this channel
您想查看此频道的内容
get recommended to you
被推荐给你
anyway stay posted for more
无论如何，请保持更新以获取更多信息
thank you very much to everyone supporting these videos
非常感谢所有支持这些视频的人
on Patreon I've been a little slow to progress
在Patreon上我进展有点慢
in the probability series
在概率序列中
this summer
今年夏天
but I'm jumping back into it after this project
但是这个项目结束后我要重新开始
so patrons you can look out for updates there
所以顾客你可以在那里寻找更新。
to close things off here
关闭这里的东西
I have with me Lisha Lee
我和丽莎·李在一起
who did her PhD
谁做了她的博士
work on the theoretical side of deep learning
深度学习理论方面的工作
and who currently works at a venture capital firm
目前在一家风险投资公司工作
called Amplify Partners
名为Amplify Partners
who kindly provided some of the funding for this video
谁好心为这个视频提供了一些资金
so lisha one thing I think we should quickly bring up
丽莎，我认为我们应该尽快提出一件事。
is this sigmoid function
这是sigmoid函数吗？
as I understand it
据我所知
early networks use this to squish the relevant
早期的网络用它来压扁相关的
weighted sum into that interval between 0 and 1
0到1之间的加权和
you know kind of
你知道有点
motivated by this biological analogy of neurons
被神经元的生物类比所驱使
either being inactive or active
不活跃或活跃
exactly but relatively
确切但相对地
few modern networks actually use sigmoid anymore
很少有现代网络真正使用sigmoid了
yeah it's kind of old school
是啊有点老派
right
对吧
yeah or rather Relu seems to be much easier to train
是的，或者更确切地说，Relu似乎更容易训练
and relu Relu stands for rectified linear unit
relu Relu代表整流线性单位
yes
是的
it's this kind of function where you're just taking
就是这种功能，你只需要
a max of 0 and
最大值为0和
a where a is given by
a其中a是由
what you were explaining in the video
你在视频中解释的内容
and what this was sort of motivated from I think was a
我认为这是出于一种动机
partially by a biological analogy with how
部分是通过生物学类比
neurons would either be activated
神经元要么被激活
or not and so if it passes a certain threshold
或者不是，所以如果它超过了某个阈值
it would be the identity function
这将是恒等函数
but if
但是如果
did not then it would just not be activated so be zero
没有，那么它就不会被激活，所以是零。
so it's kind of a simplification
所以这是一种简化
using sigmoids
使用乙状结肠
didn't help training or it was very difficult to train
没有帮助训练或者训练非常困难
it's at some point and people just tried Relu and it
在某个时候，人们刚刚尝试了Relu，它
happened to work
碰巧工作
very well for these incredibly deep neural networks
非常适合这些难以置信的深度神经网络
alright thank you Alicia
好的谢谢你Alicia